When will they stop giving to you and they don’t
Когда вам перестанут давать мы а нам не
stop giving us 2 years pass and they are
перестают 2 года проходит а нам всё
giving us more and more more and more more and
больше и больше дают всё больше и
more
больше
Hello Good evening I am from the city of
Здравствуйте Добрый вечер я из города
Khmelnitsky You are
Хмельницкий Вы
from the region I understand some warrior I
откуда й область понял какой-то вояка
see yes
вижу
in the past now I understand What are you
да в прошлом сейчас Т понял А чем сейчас
doing now  in
занимаетесь в
life, raising children is also a good
жизни воспитывать детей тоже хорошая
strategy than dying in Ukraine right now
стратегия чем сдохнуть в Украине сечас в
Yes, some questions Maybe you have what brought you
Да какие-то вопросы Может есть у вас что
here
вас сюда
to Roulette
привело в Рулетку
Yes, look at the reaction of the Ukrainians to the
Да посмотреть на реакцию украинцев на
general retreat on all
общее отступление по всем
fronts retreat look, I
фронтам отступление смотрите я правильно
understand correctly that in 202 you  they
понимаю что в 202 году вы они
have advanced, your offensive
продвинулись ваш э наступательный
potential has been knocked out, yes, now
потенциал выбили да Э теперь прилетают
Ukrainian drones are flying even to the
украинские беспилотники даже в
Leningrad region, to Tula, to a factory
Ленинградскую область в Тулу на завод
where the shell is being weakened, and you have some kind of
где панцирь роблят а вы какие-то
mythical offensive, like somewhere there
мифические наступления типа где-то там
for half a kilometer, you can explain Where and
на полкилометра можете объяснить Где и
how much you have advanced in a
на сколько вы наступили за
year  2023 What
год вот за 2023 год Какие населённые
settlements did you
пункты вы
take none everything
взяли никакие всё
that we just laugh at you
что мы ржём с вас
And we laugh at you so live Yes but we
просто А мы с вас ржём так жите Да но мы
see the idea is that we laugh and we have
смотри идея в том что мы ржём и у нас
American high-mores coming there Yes F16
поступает там американские хаймор Да F16
Storm Shadow missiles that
Шторм Shadow ракеты которые по Крыму
are hitting in the Crimea Yes and  so like yes In Czech In short,
лупят Да и сль типа да Во чеш Короче все
everyone everyone gives us everything And moreover, I don’t
все все нам дают всё И больше того я не
know whether ours are drones of our
знаю наши это беспилотники нашего
production or they were given by
производства или дали всё-таки
the Americans, but they are arriving today, flew
американцы но прилетают сегодня прилетел
to the Leningrad region, an oil
в Ленинградскую область нефтяной
terminal on the Baltic Sea cut it down
терминал на Балтийском море вырубил его
in the Tula region, a plant where shells
в тульскую область завод Где панцири
are produced  in Oryol Smolensk Belgrade
производят в Орёл Смоленск Белград
no one thinks it’s stupid anymore, they just
вообще уже никто не считает его тупо
iron the damn thing as they want and everything is like Putin
утюжат блин как хотят и всё типа и Путин
can’t do anything about it
ничего не может с этим сделать потому
because Putin is a sucker, it turns out why Putin
что Путин [__] получается почему Путин не
can’t defend
может защитить
his own You know why we laugh Why Because because
сво Знаешь почему мы ржём Почему Потому
you just listed it all
что что ты сейчас перечислил это всё то
what they gave you and tomorrow if they don’t give it to you,
что тебе дали а завтра если тебе это не
we will laugh And you have
мы А у вас
Pony, yes Well, look, it turns out, look, Well, it
у Поня да Ну смотри получается смотри Ну
turns out If yes, well, they give it to us, while they
получается Если да Ну нам дают нам пока
give it to us, and we laugh Yes,
дают и мы смеёмся
as long as you put it on you, I’ll stop giving you a
Да пока ты ты ставишь тебе перестану
[ __ ], but they give it to us A  they give us more and
[__] а нам дают А нам дают всё больше и
more and F16 they will now give F16 Yes they give And
больше и F16 дадут теперь F16 Да дают А
look at the plane This one, which
смотри самолёт Вот этот который
radar over the Sea of ​​Azov was
радиолокационный над азовским морем
shot down A50 shot down America is
сбили а50 сбили Америка
already American and the wives are already
американским есть уже да и уже жёнушки
saying they shot down everything and at once such a
говорят сбили всё и сразу такой
bread man And where is the proof and
хлебальник А где доказательство а
Belgorod is being ironed Yes A  in Crimea
Белгород утюжат утюжат Да А в Крыму
they laid down this cruiser of yours Moscow they laid down
сложили этот ваш крейсер Москва сложили
Novo Cherkas there Crimea is already all for Crimea everyone has already
Ново Черкас там Крым уже всё за Крым уже
forgotten they are hitting your military bases in
все забыли лупят ваши военные базы в
Crimea with English missiles British
Крыму английскими ракетами Британскими
British by the way Many thanks to all
британцам кстати Огромное спасибо всем
taxpayers of Great Britain for
налогоплательщикам Великобритании за
such good help in defying the orcs this is a
такую хорошую помощь в дефи орков это
very big thrill so look at you
очень большой кайф так вот смотри вы
you didn’t say correctly, if
правильно не вы правильно сказали если
they stop giving it to us, I agree,
нам перестанут давать нам Я согласен
if they stop giving it to us, you will take
если нам перестанут давать это нам вы
2-3 days and take Kiev, it’s not even
2-3 дня и возьмёте Киев это же даже не
discussed, but the trick is that they don’t
обсуждается но Фишка в том что нам не
stop giving us 2 years, and we have
перестают 2 года проходит А у нас всё
more and more help
больше и больше помощи
it’s true that you had a lot of money You
правда и и хлебало у тебя Ты же такой
were so impudent that you were just screaming And now you’re
дерзкий был токо что орал А теперь
sitting with a sour baker with a rotten nose and
сидишь с кислым хлебальник тухлым носом
now you have to pay for it You’re a fool You don’t have any more
теперь
arguments, they’re giving us more and
аргументов нам-то дают дают больше и
more
больше
help, that’s all You
помощи тебя
look, that’s all you  can you
ж всё Смотри вот всё что вы можете
tell us when they will stop giving it to you and they do
сказать когда вам перестанут давать мы а
n’t stop giving us 2 years pass and we are
нам не перестают 2 года проходит а нам
getting more and more more and more more and
всё больше и больше дают всё больше и
more we used to bomb only before it only
больше мы раньше бомбили толь раньше
flew to Belgorod we are like this in
прилетало только Белгороду мы такие по
Belgorod it arrived on the red line And
Белгороду прилетело красной линии А
now Belgorod is already like this [ __ ] well
теперь Белгород уже такой Бля ну
Belgorod well 20  people there 30 don’t
Белгород ну 20 человек там 30 вообще
give a [ __ ] about Belgrade already about Leningrad
насрать на Белград уже о Ленинград
Think about Leningrad since
Прикинь в Ленинград с сорок четвёртого
1944 no one bombed Leningrad And here
года никто не бомбил Ленинград А тут
60 years have passed, not just 60
прошло 60 лет не каких 60
Hello 80 years and Ukraine is bombing Leningrad
Алло 80 лет и Украина бомбит Ленинград
This is not a sign This is a sign look you [ __ ] up
Это не знак Это знак смотри вы просрали
Leningrad Where is your air defense Putin is not  can
Ленинград Где ваше ПВО Путин не может
protect Everything, you crap America,
защитить Всё вы обосрались Америка
look First, why not, if seriously, the
смотри Сначала почему нет если серьёзно
first 2-3 days we thought that you would
первые 2-3 дня мы думали что вы
capture Kiev, yes America also
захватите Киев да Америка также
pissed himself, he thinks everything will be captured now
обоссалась думает всё сейчас захватят
Kiev won’t help anyone Yes, they’re
Киев не бут кому помогать Да бриты
only shaved Well done, they showered us with all sorts of
только Молодцы нас закидали там всякими
goodies there Ukraine repelled the Russian attack
плюшками Украина отбила российскую атаку
everyone  understood about Russia is weak, you can
все поняли о Россия слабая можно Украину
pump up Ukraine, pump up Yes, they pumped up the pancake
накачивать накачивать Да накачали блин
like a piston with these weapons you carry Russia, they knocked them out
как поршень этим оружием вы носит Россию
of the Kiev region, Sumy
выбили с Киевской области Сумской
Chernigov, Zhitomir, Kharkov, from Kherson,
Черниговской Житомирской Харьковской с
from the Nikolaev region, Yes, he just
Херсона с Николаевской области Да просто
shamefully ran away and everyone is like that Oh, so Russia is a
позорно убежал и все такие О так Россия
sucker state, yes they said the red
государство [__] да говорили красной
line is a blow to the Crimea  They're hitting Crimea And that's it And
линии удар по Крыму по Крыму бьют И всё
that your nuclear weapons in Belgorod are
И что ваше ядерное оружие по Белгороду
stupid Belgorod is being demolished and leveled with the ground like
тупо Белгород сносят ровняют землёй как
10 years Donbass stupidly understand Putin I
10 лет Донбасс тупо понимаешь Путин я
will protect Donbass And now you can't
защищу Донбасс А теперь не можеш
protect
защитить
Belgorod St. Petersburg in general and here
Белгород санк-петербург вообще и у нас
America is watching [ __ ] so
нас Америка смотрит Бля так это ж
cool look you can  load Ukraine with
классно смотри можно заряжать Украину
huge different weapons Let them
огромным разным оружием Пусть они нахрен
[ __ ] out all these bases, the military in Russia are
выносят все эти базы военные в России
sinking ships no matter how many
топят кораблики сколько
ships, not a single American ship
корабле ни один американский корабль не
has sunk, and there are
потонул ни один а а российских уже
more and more Russian Russians.
российских всё больше и больше Феодосию
split and everything and everything
осколками натами расщеп да и всё и всё
you started so impudently impudent And now you are
ты начал такой дерзкий дерзкий А теперь
sitting and
сидишь и
sitting, let’s subscribe to my
сидел давай так подпишись на мий
Telegram right now, the axis of wine and
Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
bye you are more and more
пок це дуже и дуже
respectful
важливо